MARCELO ANDRES PEREZ

mandresperez.uk@gmail.com | Denver, CO | (323) 371-7601 linkedin.com/in/marcelo-perez-7728b910a | github.com/mandresp

Profile Summary

Recently graduated Full Stack Developer with over five years Marketing and Real Estate work experience as well as dual International Business/Economics degree. Adaptive – Multi-cultural having lived in the US, Hong Kong and London. Fluent in written and spoken Mandarin and conversationally fluent in Cantonese. Creative – Skilled in Art/Design/Music.

Technical Skills

HTML | CSS | Javascript | JQuery | GraphQL | MERN Stack | Python | Bootstrap | Adobe Creative Suite | Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint) | Salesforce | MLS | CoStar | Pardot | Constant Contact | Landvision

Education

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP - ONLINE CERTIFICATE

- Gained hands-on experience and technical understanding of MERN stack & Bootstrap.
- Generated new code for three agile projects, Git-based source control, and Heroku-based deployment.
 - o **HOWDYNEIGHBOR** Deployed Site: <u>HOWDYNEIGHBOR</u> Repository: <u>GitHub</u>
 - Constructed all page routes and assisted in the front-end design of the site.
 - dreamStream
 Deployed Site: <u>dreamStream</u>
 Repository: <u>GitHub</u>
 - Designed the front end of the site including artwork and branding.
 - Deployed Site: Where ISS It? Repository: GitHub
 - Built the front end of the application and oversaw design choices.

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH CAROLINA & CHINESE UNIVERSITY OF HONG KONG JOINT PROGRAM - INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS AND CHINESE ENTERPRISE

Bachelor of Science - Dual Major: International Business & Economics, Minor: Chinese Language

Professional Experience

TARGET, RECEIVER - Denver, CO 2021-2023

- Responsible for receiving the general merchandise daily trailer.
- Perform weekly inventory audits for the whole store.
- Complete three weekly orders to stock the fresh market.
- Manage all shipments of ESIM, store to store transfers, and inventory removals.

JAMES CAPITAL ADVISORS, MARKETING ASSOCIATE – Los Angeles, CA 2019 – 2020 (moved agencies with partners from Marcus & Millichap)

- Created marketing material for multifamily & net lease listings for 50+ agents using InDesign & Photoshop.
- Worked with agents to understand each listing's selling points to best market the property.
- Edited photos through the use of Photoshop, Lightroom, & Luminar.
- Created site plans for listings through the use of Photoshop.
- Created & scheduled email blasts for clients through the use of Pardot & Salesforce.

MARCUS & MILLICHAP, MARKETING & CLIENT SERVICES ASSISTANT – Los Angeles, CA 2018 - 2019

- Created marketing material for 6 agents through the use of Adobe InDesign & Photoshop.
- Sourced rent & sales comparables & helped underwrite multifamily apartment buildings.
- Created & scheduled email blasts for clients through the use of Constant Contact.
- Prepared physical BOVs for meetings with clients.